Hello, this is the team members feature created on
V2 to make things easier
for lpshares users to use it.
You just need to come to the members
tab and click the invite members button.
So there are two ways.
You can either invite an
existing lpshares user or you can invite
a new user as a member of your team.
So we'll start with inviting
an existing lpshares user.
So I'll invite this user.
You send, send invite.
Invitation sent successfully.
And I'll check that mail.
So the user should receive a mail like this
you have been invited, then they can log in.
So this is the user that was sent the invite.
I refresh this page.
You can see that the team
account is now available.
So you have the personal account and the team
account so you can switch to the team account.
Then you should see the listings.
So if you notice the listings here.
And the listings here.
They are the same and also the bids.
They are the same, so you can use.
So each team member can.
You know, create listings, make bids.
And it'll be synced for both accounts.
And also drive upload files to the drive.
So to switch to the switch back to
your personal account for a member.
So you see the listings have changed.
To the personal account.
You can also invite a user that
is not on the platform yet.
And they'll get an email.
If I check the email now.
And they should receive this email.
And once the user sets up their account.
Then you can come back here and invite
them as an existing lpshares user
and they'll be added to your team.
they can manage your listings, manage
your bids, and upload and edit documents.
So that's the team members feature on V2.